# JONAR BONDOC ISIP

# IT SPECIALIST

P 714-371-7219

E jisip1@gmail.com

A Corona, CA

W

www.jbisip.com

#### **SUMMARY**

A technically minded professional that seeks to offer a fresh perspective, backed by 20-years of experience working in busy office environments, analyzing large data sets and problem solving. Eternally curious, a fast learner and a patient teacher.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### November 2020 - January 2021

Quality Control Inspector III | Metrology | Jabil Inc.

Monitored calibration dates of measurement assets per ISO 9001

#### January 2018 - September 2020

Production Planning and Scheduler | ArmaninoLLP

• Provided training and technical support to Workfront users

#### June 2016 - December 2017

Project Coordinator | Wells Fargo

Generated project status reports and checked them for completeness

#### May 2011 - June 2016

Quality Control Supervisor | Advanced Measurement Labs

Developed process documentation for company inspection equipment

#### July 2010 - May 2011

Lead Quality Control Inspector | Advanced Measurement Labs

Created and refined automation scripts for company's CNC CMMs

#### August 2009 - June 2010

Quality Control Inspector | TC Quality Machining

Brought mothballed CMM back into production and trained in its use

#### February 2000 - June 2007

Quality Control Inspector | Advanced Measurement Labs

Designed and implemented company's first LAN

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

CompTIA Security+: May 2021

Google IT Automation with Python Prof. Cert. – planned for Aug 2021

### **EDUCATION**

University of California Riverside Riverside, CA Class of 2007

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- TROUBLESHOOTING
- TRAINING
- DOCUMENTATION
- PROJECT MANAGEMENT
- ASSET MANAGEMENT
- PYTHON SCRIPTS
- REPORTS

## SOFTWARE/OS

- WINDOWS 20 YEARS
- MAC OS 10 YEARS
- PYTHON I YEAR
- VBA 3 YEARS
- HYPER-V I YEAR
- LINUX I YEAR
- WORKFRONT 2 YEARS

#### **INTERESTS**

- PC BUILDING
- PHOTOGRAPHY
- PHOTO/VIDEO EDITING